The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Did you hear ?
Someone is targeted by the Hundred Days Execution Order.
He also killed a group of Core Formation cultivators.
I heard ! Even the Grand Elder was killed !
This is too sinister...
Is he Nascent Soul ?
This is... wait...
It's him !
Run ! Quick !
This fiend broke Xue Ming's formation
like it was nothing...
If we obey him,
we might be able to survive.
This person's strength is terrifying.
We must be very careful.
It seems becoming his disciple was the right choice.
If I follow him,
I'll be able to do as I please
in the outer Sea of Devils.
I need to establish a foothold in the Sea of Devils
and the Fighting Evil Sect is my best choice for that.
I used a bit too much of my Ji Realm earlier
but it's okay.
It should recover quickly
if I nourish it within my Sea of Consciousness.
He actually did it....
From now on,
I am the strongest person below Nascent Soul.
When I first met him,
I thought he was Sun Youcai.
I nearly caused a misunderstanding.
Had we really fought back then,
he would've slaughtered everyone present.
He wouldn't even have shown an ounce of mercy towards me.
You don't need to worry.
After I'm done with all this,
I'll take you back to the Burning Fire Alliance.
Fellow cultivator afflicted by the Hundred Days Execution Order,
Grand Elder Qian Kun provoked you
and killing him was justified.
You already killed dozens of our disciples.
However...
Do you truly think my Fighting Evil Sect is made of lambs to prey on ?
Formation !
10 000 cultivators in a formation...
The headquarters of the Fighting Evil Sect has 13 562 members
and they're all here !
The Great Dragon Formation actually exists !
Xie Donglai\NFighting Evil Sect Leader\NLate stage Core Formation
The Great Dragon Formation is the protection formation of the Fighting Evil Sect.
Unless you are a Nascent Soul cultivator,
it's impossible to break.
The formation isn't fully active yet.
My brother and I are Elders of a branch of the sect
Please let us negotiate with the Sect Leader for you.
Yes, yes !
We can still stop the formation now.
Once it's activated,
it will be too late.
Are you trying to pull a trick in front of Master ?
No need, just take care of Miss Li.
Understood.
Senior !
Be careful...
They need to set up this big formation
so it's the perfect time to attack.
Formation, activate !
His cultivation...
went from Late stage to Peak Late stage Core Formation !
Wait,
he's still breaking through !
This is...
Xie Donglai\NFighting Evil Sect Leader\NFalse Nascent Soul
False Nascent Soul realm...
False Nascent Soul
is below Early stage Nascent Soul.
But it's infinitely close to Nascent Soul.
The Fighting Evil Sect
doesn't accept traitors.
I thought he would win
but now the situation has changed...
He will lose !
He still has my Soul Blood...
If he dies,
I will die alongside him !
This Great Dragon Formation
must have some kind of weakness !
I have heard
the rumors about
what you did along the way.
No one below Nascent Soul can beat you.
But now, my cultivation is the equivalent of Nascent Soul !
Let's see if you can defeat me !
This formation...
The Myriad Blood Demon Formation...
I know that you broke
that traitor Xue Ming's Myriad Blood Demon Formation.
But the formation was only
a tenth of the power of the Great Dragon Formation !
You've gathered the spiritual energy
of 10 000 people on yourself.
You just temporarily increased your cultivation.
With my cultivation, it will only take an instant
to kill you !
Since I could break that Myriad Blood Demon Formation,
then I can break the Great Dragon Formation too !
You fool.
The might of a Nascent Soul
is not something a Junior like you can resist !
Since it operates like the Myriad Blood Demon Formation...
...he just needs to find its core !
Mere tricks !
The dragon's head !
Splendid !
It's been 100 years
since I have seen someone attack the formation !
It's time to eat !
A... a Nascent Soul cultivator !?
Wang Lin, you damn fiend !
Who gave you the audacity to challenge
our mighty sect
with such little strength ?
Mighty sect ?
You're too pretentious.
What ?
What the hell is this thing ?!
Grandpa Xu is the first demon of the world !
I must kill this monster today
in the name of the heavens !
Junior, you're no match for the teleportation
of the Nascent Soul level.
The formation... isn't broken !?
Did you think that our sect protection formation would break easily ?
If this formation is invincible,
then if enough people fuel it
it might even give Soul Formation level cultivation.
If that's true,
why didn't the Fighting Evil Sect invade South Dipper City ?
This formation must have a fatal weakness.
Could it be...
Neither you or your friends
will be able to escape !
Kill them !
Go ahead and try !
That old ghost Xie Donglai
is playing dirty !
That's good...
If she gets injured,
I probably won't live either.
It's not that easy to break my golden bowl !
The Fighting Evil Sect is lacking females.
From now on,
you belong to me !
You...
can die.
Senior !
Senior Brother, you're injured...
Master, fighting a Nascent Soul as a Core Formation
isn't possible.
We should retreat for now.
This Great Dragon Formation can't be broken by Core Formation cultivators.
We really should retreat.
Am I going to die here ?
Help ! Help me !
We won't retreat.
Be reasonable and give me your Golden Cores now.
If you don't, none of you will survive !
He can't hold on !
Are they the same strength now ?
Xie Donglai is retreating !
Could he already be tired ?
And now he's stronger...
This is the end of this battle !
No !
One last test.
Just as I thought.
Senior !
Master !
Are you alright ?
I found the way to beat the Great Dragon Formation.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?